## **HILBER FRAIESE**

#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

#### **PROFFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

I am a well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. I can handle any part of the process with no difficulties. I am a collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering over two years of related experience. I am passionate about new technologies and learning to apply them.

### **WORK HISTORY**

## Full Stack Developer, 10/2021 to current Econocom, Mexico, Mexico City

Creation of APIs, end to end, and microservices for the integration of different projects.

Design and creation of Database, relational and non-relational.

API deployment in AWS or Azure. Conducting tests through Jest and Cypress Front End support, helping in the implementation of services with React and Redux libraries.

# Teaching Assistant for Full Stack Development students, 7/2021 to 7/2022 Soy Henry, Argentina, Buenos Aires

Coordinate a group of students to achieve integration to the study group.
Guide students in the first steps of the course

Assist in the resolution of exercises and promote group collaboration (Pair Programming)

Propose ideas for the improvement of the Bootcamp processes

#### CONTACT

Address: Mar del Plata, Argentina

Phone: +5492235421793

Email: hilberfraiese92@gmail.com

**Linkedin:** Hilber Fraiese

**Portfolio:** https://hilber-fraiese.web.app **GitHub:** https://github.com/Hilberfraiese

#### **SKILLS**

- Scripting Language: Javascript, Typescript.
- Front-End Skills: HTML, CSS, React, Redux, Styled Component, Sass.
- Back-end Skills: Node.Js, NestJs.
- Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Oracle. Other technologies:
- AWS (S3 EC2 Load Balancer Lambda Tasks etc)
- Azure (AKS Blob Storage)
- Github | BitBucket

#### Soft Skills:

- Reading Comprehension
- Creative Solution Development
- Simulation Leadership

#### **LANGUAGES**

Spanish: Native language

English: B1

Intermediate

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Full Stack Developer Bootcamp Soy Henry, 04/2021 to 09/2021

Bootcamp Full Stack Developer with over 1000 hours of study.

Learned technologies: Javascript | React | Redux | HTML | CSS | Node.Js| MySQL | PostgreSQL | MongoDB

## Senior technician in programming UTN(NATIONAL TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY)

03/2010 to 06/2011

Database design and administration Mathematics and Statistics Computers science Skills: Turbo Pascal | C++